

Emir Mertoğlu Front-End Developer

+905303001197

🔀 emir.mertoglu.97@gmail.com

nemirxmertoglu

in emirmertoglu

M emirmertoglu

emirxmertoglu

Professional Experience

Bootcamp Participant, Erka React Bootcamp

05/2022 - 05/2022

At the end of the Bootcamp, I've learned the below things:

- · Components and Props
- · State and Lifecycle
- Forms
- Context API
- React Router

Intern Front-End Developer, T-Soft □

02/2022 - 05/2022

- I build thoroughly modern and responsive websites.
- Mainly focused on: SASS, JavaScript, and our UI library based on Skeleton.

Paramedic, Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University Training and

04/2019 - 02/2022

Research Hospital

I used to work as a nurse at the emergency care service until I complete my bachelor's degree but I quit the job before completing my bachelor's degree because I want to be focused on my new career path.

Bootcamp Participant,

11/2021 - 01/2022

Gelecek Varlık FullStack Bootcamp ☑

At the end of the Bootcamp, I've learned the below things:

- .NET Core and React.
- N-Tier Architecture.
- · Restful API.

Intern Front-End Developer, Nutima Code 🗷

03/2021 - 10/2021

- I built thoroughly modern and responsive websites.
- · Mainly focused on: JavaScript and Vue.js.

🕅 Skills

React

Vue.ls

JavaScript

jQuery

Node.Js

HTML5

CSS3

SASS

Gulp

Git

JSON

Firebase

Profile

I have hands-on experience efficiently coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Building state-of-the-art, easy-to-use, user-friendly websites and applications is truly a passion of mine and I am confident I would be an excellent addition to the organization that I work for. In addition to my knowledge base, I actively seek out new technologies and stay up-to-date on industry trends and advancements.

Projects

Vue Color Picker □

A super simple color picker component for Vue.Js. Click to preview the project. ☑

V-Book 🗷

A web app where you can view the top 100 classical books. I use Vue.Js & Vue Router & Json-Server with this project

Vue Web Form 🛮

A web form based on Vue.Js v3. Click to preview the project. 🛮

Vue Kanban Board 🖂

A Kanban Board Todo App with Vue.Js 2, Vue Router, Firebase, and Bootstrap-Vue. Click to preview the project. 🗷

Reaction Timer 7

A reaction game built with Vue.Js v3. Click here to play the game. ☑

Vue ToDo App 🗷

Super basic Vue.Js 3 Todo App coded with Composition API. Click to preview the project. 🗷

COVID-19 Turkey Data 🗗

My goal in this project is to analyze the coronavirus data in the data set to make it meaningful and visualize it.

Kaggle link 🛮

Stuvent Mobile, for IEEEmadC | Mobile Application Development Contest 🗷

My goal in this project is to announce the events that will take place at the university through the mobile application.

Organisations

GDG Mugla, Organizer and Developer ☑

09/2020 - 03/2021

When you join a Google Developer Group, you'll have the opportunity to meet local developers with similar interests in technology. A GDG meetup event includes talks on a wide range of technical topics where you can learn new skills through hands-on workshops. The community prides itself on being an inclusive environment where everyone and anyone interested in tech - from beginner developers to experienced professionals - all are welcome to join.

- I organized and helped with some events.
- I developed the GDG&WTM Mugla website.

DSC MSKU, Core Team Member 🗆

08/2019 - 08/2020

Developer Student Clubs are university-based community groups for students interested in Google developer technologies. By joining a DSC, students grow their knowledge in a peer-to-peer learning environment and build solutions for local businesses and their community.

• I organized and helped with some events.

Education

Information Systems Engineering,

09/2018 - 06/2022

Mugla Sitki Kocman University

GPA: 3.63

I graduated from my university with the first place in my department and my faculty.

Management of Health Institutions,

09/2015 - 06/2018

Anadolu University

Paramedic, Nisantasi University

09/2015 - 06/2017

Awards

Certificate of Achievement, Prof. Dr. Hüseyin ÇİÇEK

06/2022

I congratulate your academic performance at our university, your efforts to be entrepreneurial, innovative and individuals with high national awareness, and I wish you a life full of success with the belief that you will always work hard in line with our country's strong Turkey ideal.

Certificate of Achievement, Prof. Dr. Hilmi TOKER

01/2022

I congratulate you on your project titled "E-Parent Artificial Intelligence Supported Baby Growth Application", which was deemed worthy of support within the scope of "TÜBİTAK 2209/A University Students Research Projects Support Program" and wish you continued success.

Certificate of Appreciation, Assoc. Dr. Turhan TOGAN

03/2021

Dear Emir Mertoğlu, your support for our healthcare delivery during the fight against the Covid-19 Pandemic; I congratulate you for the dedication and sacrifice you have shown in our work and wish you continued success in your professional life.

Certificate of Honor, Prof. Dr. Naci GÜNDOĞAN

06/2016

Due to his success in the spring semester of the 2015-2016 academic year, he was entitled to receive this document.

Certificate of Honor, Prof. Dr. Naci GÜNDOĞAN

02/2016

Due to his success in the fall semester of the 2015-2016 academic year, he was entitled to receive this document.

☆ Certificates

Beginner Frontend Web Development Path

JavaScript, Data Structures and Algorithms, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML, GIT, Visual Studio Code, Essential Lessons for Everyone

Gelecek Varlık Fullstack Bootcamp 🛭

.Net Core and React, N-Tier Architecture, Restful API.

Cisco Networking Academy Introduction to Cybersecurity course, and demonstrating the ability to explain the following:

Global implications of cyber threats, Ways in which networks are vulnerable to attack, Impact of cyber-attacks on industries, Cisco's approach to threats detection and defense

Cisco Networking Academy Mobility Fundamentals course, and demonstrating the ability to do following:

Wireless technologies, Wireless LAN standarts, Wireless LAN access point, router and client, Wireless LAN security, troubleshoot Wireless LANs

Computer Aided Advertising and Design 2

I can use most Adobe Technologies: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, etc. Certificate ID: 16012820170051199318

Computer Usage

I can use most modern computers. Certificate ID: 16012820160044790907

ECG & Pharmacology Course

by the American Heart Association

& Languages

EnglishProfessional working competence
Native